import { Levels, Categories } from '../../src/utils/config';

export default [
  {
    category: Categories.FIELD,
    question: 'The dimensions of an outdoor field are :',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: '90m x 30m',
      b: '97m x 35m',
      c: '100m x 37m',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['c'],
    explanation: 'See the diagram in Chapter 2 of the rules.',
    rules: undefined,
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.EASY,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.PULL,
    question:
      'Upon receiving a pull, an attacker unintentionally touches the disc with her leg, then the disc hits the ground uncaught.',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'The move was unintentional, the attackers retain possession of the disc where it touched him',
      b: "Turnover because she didn't catch it",
      c: 'Not having touched it with the hand, the attackers recover the disc at the point where it stops or goes out',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['b'],
    explanation: "It is a 'dropped pull'. The voluntary or involuntary aspect does not enter in consideration.",
    rules: ['7.8.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.EASY,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.PULL,
    question: "On the pull, the disc lands and comes to rest in the opponent's end zone",
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'Attackers can play it where it hits the ground or where it comes to rest',
      b: 'The attackers have the choice to play it where it stopped or at the entrance of the zone',
      c: 'The attackers must play it from the place where it came to rest',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['c'],
    explanation:
      'If the disc does not contact out of bounds as a result of a pull, the thrower must play it where it stopped.',
    rules: ['7.10.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.MIDDLE,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.FIELD,
    question: 'The line that delimits the playing area',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'is considered part of the playing area',
      b: 'is considered not to be part of the playing area',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['b'],
    explanation: 'In ultimate, the lines are not part of the field.',
    rules: ['11.1.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.EASY,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.PULL,
    question:
      'The pull exits the field from one side without having made contact with the ground. The thrower can put her pivot foot',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'at the brick mark, or at midfield, or at the sideline where the disc went out',
      b: 'at the brick mark, or in the middle of the end line',
      c: 'at the brick mark, or at the point on the sideline where the disc came out',
      d: 'at the brick mark, or at the point on the sideline closest to where the disc landed',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['c'],
    explanation: 'It is up to the attacking team to choose.',
    rules: ['7.12.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.MIDDLE,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.COUNT,
    question:
      "A player has just dived for the disc. As soon as it lands on his chest, the defender says 'stalling' and starts counting",
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'The defender must wait for the player to get up before starting to count',
      b: 'The defender does not have to wait for the player to get up before starting to count',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['b'],
    explanation:
      'The defender may count if he/she is within 3 meters of the thrower and does not commit a scoring infraction.',
    rules: ['9.3.', '9.3.1.', '9.3.2.', '9.3.3.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.MIDDLE,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.FIELD,
    question:
      'An attacker catches the disc in the air and lands with one foot in the playing area and one foot on the sideline. Both feet touch the ground at the same time.',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'Turnover',
      b: 'Not a turnover',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['a'],
    explanation: "The attacker's first point of contact is out of bounds.",
    rules: ['11.4.', '11.4.1.', '11.4.2.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.MIDDLE,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.RECEIVER,
    question: 'An attacker and a defender catch the disc at exactly the same time',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'Defender gains possession of the disc',
      b: 'Attacker gains possession of the disc',
      c: 'The disc returns to the thrower',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['b'],
    explanation: 'And the game is not stopped unless a discussion is needed to resolve the situation.',
    rules: ['12.3.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.EASY,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.COUNT,
    question: 'For a stall-out, the thrower must still be in possession of the disc when',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: "the marker starts to say 'Stall', after reaching ten",
      b: "the marker finishes saying 'Stall', after reaching ten",
      c: "the marker starts to say 'ten",
      d: "the marker finishes saying 'ten",
    },
    correctAnswers: ['c'],
    explanation:
      "It is the 'd' in 'ten' that marks the end of the count. The call 'Stall-out' simply means that 'ten' has been reached.",
    rules: ['13.2.', '13.2.2.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.EASY,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.GOAL,
    question: 'An attacker catches the disc in the end zone he is attacking. Then he throws an incomplete pass',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'It is a turnover',
      b: "No turnover, that's a point",
    },
    correctAnswers: ['b'],
    explanation:
      "The point is scored at the moment of the catch, whether the attacker is aware of it or not. The failed pass attempt afterwards does not matter because the point is already scored (provided that someone called 'point' on the field).",
    rules: ['14.4.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.DIFFICULT,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.CONTINUATION,
    question: 'The thrower is fouled while pivoting. She calls the foul and then attempts the pass',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'If the pass is completed, play continues',
      b: 'If the pass is not completed, play continues',
      c: 'The disc returns to the thrower regardless of the outcome of the pass',
      d: "The thrower can only call 'Contact' when the contact occurs outside the throwing motion",
    },
    correctAnswers: ['c'],
    explanation: "The play stops immediately when the thrower calls 'foul', so the pass is ignored.",
    rules: ['16.1.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.MIDDLE,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.FOULS,
    question:
      'An attacker touches the disc in the air while trying to catch it, but is unsuccessful. The defender then fouls the attacker and prevents him from making a second attempt to catch the disc',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: "This is a 'Strip' foul",
      b: 'This is not a foul because the striker had already missed his catch',
      c: 'It is a foul because the attacker was prevented from catching the disc on his second attempt',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['c'],
    explanation: '',
    rules: ['17.2.1.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.MIDDLE,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.INFRACTIONS_VIOLATIONS,
    question: "Thrower calls 'Disc Space' and scorer challenges",
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'The game stops',
      b: "The game doesn't stop",
      c: 'The scorer cannot challenge a scoring infraction',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['a'],
    explanation: 'The game would not have stopped if the infraction had been accepted.',
    rules: ['18.1.2.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.MIDDLE,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.CONTINUATION,
    question:
      'A travel is called against the thrower before she makes the pass. The thrower attempts the pass, but it is not completed.',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'Turnover. The game continues without a check',
      b: 'Turnover. The game continues after a check',
      c: 'Turnover only if travel is not contested',
      d: 'The disc comes back to the thrower',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['a'],
    explanation: '',
    rules: ['18.2.8.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.DIFFICULT,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.INFRACTIONS_VIOLATIONS,
    question:
      'A defender tries to follow the player he is defending, but he runs into one of his teammates. The thrower still has the disc',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: "It's not a pick because they are in the same team",
      b: "It's a pick, but the play doesn't stop if the attacker doesn't receive the disc",
      c: 'This is a pick. The play stops and the defender can catch up',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['c'],
    explanation:
      'This is a pick. The defender can also take 2 seconds before calling it to check if it has an impact on the game or not.',
    rules: ['18.3.1.', '18.3.1.1.', '18.3.2.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.EASY,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.FIELD,
    question:
      'After establishing his pivot foot in the field, one player completes his pass by putting the other out-of-bounds',
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'He had a turnover because he had one foot out of the field',
      b: 'There is no turnover',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['b'],
    explanation: 'With the pivot foot established in the field, the player is considered onside.',
    rules: ['11.3.3.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.MIDDLE,
  },
  {
    category: Categories.CONTINUATION,
    question: "On an accepted 'Stall-out",
    image: undefined,
    answerChoices: {
      a: 'Turnover, it is the marker that regains possession of the disc',
      b: 'Turnover and any attacker can take the disc back, after a check',
    },
    correctAnswers: ['b'],
    explanation:
      'Any attacker may take possession of the disc after a turnover except after an interception (in which case the player who made the interception must maintain possession) or after an offensive receiving foul (in which case the player who suffered the foul must take possession)',
    rules: ['13.5.', '13.5.1.', '13.5.2.'],
    source: 'DFEU - Pablo',
    level: Levels.MIDDLE,
  },
];
